He is such a bore.
These are all to be typed tonight,
signed by you
and sent first post tomorrow.
This is to Duke Michail Michailovich
asking after his health
and suggesting
an alternative date for lunch.
This one is to Lady Lewington.
It is quite flirtatious
but I hear she is a whore
and will respond.
And this is to Mr. Shelby.
He has the effrontery
to check our sapphires,
we need proof
he has the material we require,
at a time of our choosing.
How much did you drink?
Wine, no vodka.
At the end of this business
you may have to kill Mr. Shelby yourself.
Can you do it?
Of course.
He will catch the train
from Naples to Paris
and then the boat train to London.
And he can be here by Sunday, yes?
Kill!